<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configuration file on CLIO</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configuration file on CLIO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workflow name</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/workflow_name/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/workflow_name/index.html</guid>
      <description>This section is identified by the keyword name. The name is used as an identifier for the current application workflow. This is useful as it is possible to distinguish different application workflows running on the same machine.
Example { &amp;#34;name&amp;#34; :&amp;#34;my_workflow&amp;#34;, }</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alias</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/alias/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/alias/index.html</guid>
      <description>Alias section The aliases section, identified by the keyword aliases is useful to reduce the verbosity of the enumeration of files an application can consume or produce. It is a vector of objects composed of the following items:
group_name: the alias identifier files: an array of strings representing file names. Example The following snippet is a valid alias section for CLIO configuration language
{ &amp;#34;name&amp;#34; : &amp;#34;my_workflow&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;aliases&amp;#34; : [ { &amp;#34;group_name&amp;#34; : &amp;#34;group-even&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;files&amp;#34; : [&amp;#34;file0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I/O Graph</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/io_graph/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/io_graph/index.html</guid>
      <description>This section defines the dependencies between input and output streams between application modules comprising the workflow. It is identified by the keyword IO_Graph, and it requires an array of objects. Those objects specify the input and output streams for each application component. Each object defines the following items:
name: The name of the application. This keyword is mandatory input_stream: This keyword identifies the input files and directories the application module is expected to read.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Permanent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/permanent/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/permanent/index.html</guid>
      <description>This language section, identified by the keyword permanent, is used to specify those files that will be stored on the filesystem at the end of the workflow execution. Its value is an array of file names (whose values can be also aliases).
Example The following snippet is a valid example of how the permanent section should be specified:
{ &amp;#34;name&amp;#34; :&amp;#34;my_workflow&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;permanent&amp;#34; :[&amp;#34;output.dat&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;group0&amp;#34; ] }At the end of the execution of “my_workflow”, the file output.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclude</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/exclude/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/exclude/index.html</guid>
      <description>This section, identified by the keyword exclude, is used to specify those files that will not be handled by CLIO even if they will be created inside the CLIO_DIR directory. Its value is an array of file names (whose values can also be aliases).
Example The following snippet is a valid section for the exclude section:
{ &amp;#34;name&amp;#34; :&amp;#34;my_workflow&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;exclude&amp;#34; :[&amp;#34;file1.dat&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;group0&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;*.tmp&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;*~&amp;#34; ] }</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home node policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/home_node_policy/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/configuration_file/home_node_policy/index.html</guid>
      <description>This section allows the CLIO user to selectively choose the CLIO server node where all files (or a subset of them) and their associated metadata should be stored. The user can define different policies for different files. In the current version of the CLIO language, the home node policy options are:
create (default option) manual hashing These three keywords are optional, i.e., the user can avoid setting them explicitly in the CLIO configuration file.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>